xtreemhost.com 2009-04-30

# Privacy policy | XtreemHost

XtreemHost considers your privacy and protecting your personal information very seriously. Our Privacy Policy governs what is done with your information, how we handle your information and who gets your information.

Each visitor to our web page passively generates information which includes the IP address, browser string, referrer and general geo-location information about the visitor among other items of information automatically.

Where possible, we collect the domain name of the visitor but not the e-mail address unless required such as those whom become members of our forums or signup for our service(s), aggregate information on what pages the visitor accesses, information volunteered by the visitor such as registration data, survey or poll information which may include the visitor’s full name, address, and payment information among other things.

Information collected is used for a number of purposes including for internal review in terms of passively collected data, for improving the content of our site, to notify our members about updates or service announcements for those who register for our services and is shared with other reputable organizations who may contact our visitors for various reasons including marketing purposes.

In respect to cookies, we utilize cookies to store visitor preferences, record session information and to maintain access to secure areas when it comes to your account.

If in the event you do not wish to receive e-mail from us or our trusted partners, please follow instructions included in the e-mail to request removal of your address from the system. Your opting out of such mailings does not affect e-mail messages regarding your accounts, services or other important information that affects your service directly from us.

If you have supplied us with your postal mailing address online, you will only receive information and messages for which you provided us your postal address.

If you have supplied us with your telephone number online, you will only receive telephone contact from us regarding orders you have place on our site or with our services.

In respect to advertising, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place advertising on our website and on your XtreemHost FREE web pages. As a result of your visit to our site or to a client site, advertising companies may collect information such as your domain type, IP address and clickstream information. For further information, please consult the privacy policy of Google Inc.

From time to time, we may utilize viewer and customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy policy. If our information practices change at some point in the future, we will post a revised policy to our website to notify you of these changes and, at our discretion, provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.

Of course, if you are concerned about how your information is or will be used, you should occasionally check the privacy policy page of our website.

Upon request, we may provide customers and members with access to information we have collected and that we maintain about them provided said request is not overly taxing or burdensome upon our staff.

We offer customers and members the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in their contact information and financial information either via user-controlled function or via contact form.

In respect to security, when certain information is transmitted either to or from our systems such as your financial details, we redirect visitors to a third-party secured server to ensure the integrity of the information and the request which benefits both the visitor and XtreemHost.

Privacy Policy last updated: November 9, 2008.
